Guide to the Harry Adams Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Identified Subjects, 1951–1985
  - Sites and Events Outside California
    - Las Vegas, Nevada
      - Exterior view of the Dunes Hotel and Casino in Las Vegas, Nevada, 1975 September (Box 9, Folder 456)
    - Miami, Florida
      - Interior portrait of Connie Alexander and Syble Johnson of the at a buffet during a meeting of Travel Age in Miami, Florida, 1984 October (Box 9, Folder 457)
    - Morocco
      - Exterior portrait of a guard with a spear in Morocco, circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 458)
      - Exterior portraits of three women in Morocco, circa 1980; 2 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 459)
      - Exterior views of a music and dance performance in Morocco, circa 1980; 4 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 460)
      - Interior portrait of Ei Mustafa Raguigus with a woman and two men in Morocco, circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 461)
      - Interior view of a group eating a meal in Morocco, circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 462)
      - Interior views of a music and dance performance, including belly dancing, in Morocco, circa 1980; 7 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 463)
- Unidentified Subjects, 1951–1985
  This series consists of photographic material created by Harry Adams with unidentified subjects, 1951-1985.
  Series II is organized into two subseries: Unidentified Subjects with Dates and Unidentified Subjects without Dates.
  - Unidentified Subjects with Dates
    This subseries consists of photographic material created by Harry Adams with unidentified subjects but with dates, 1951-1985. Many of the photographic prints have ink stamped dates on versos.
    Subseries arranged chronologically.
    - Interior portrait of five men, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 464)
    - Exterior portrait of two girls and a boy, 1953 July 12; 2 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - Interior portrait of a man, probably an employee of Adams' studio, and a female dancer, 1954 October 28 (Box 10, Folder 466)
      The man has a film negative holder in his jacket pocket
    - Exterior view of a 1955 Buick Century automobile, 1955 March 4 (Box 10, Folder 467)
    - Interior portrait of a woman holding a trumpet, a man at a piano, and another man, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 468)
    - Interior view of a large group of chiefly men on a television production set, possible in a residence, with a female performer and a older woman with an infant, circa 1955 (Box 10, Folder 469)
    - Exterior portrait of two women and a man posed sitting on a wooden wagon with a donkey in Tijuana, Mexico, 1956 June 28 (Box 10, Folder 470)
    - Interior portrait of one woman and two men, 1959 September 27 (Box 10, Folder 471)
    - Studio portrait of a woman, 1959 October (Box 10, Folder 472)
    - Interior portrait of thirty-one men, possibly liquor distributors, 1960 April 22 (Box 10, Folder 473)
    - Interior portrait of a man dancing, 1960 May 8 (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and two men, 1960 October 12 (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - Exterior portrait of a woman with a Ford Fairlane 500 automobile, 1960 October 29 (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - Exterior view of police officers and civilians, probably at the scene of an automobile accident, circa 1960 (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - Interior portrait of man holding a bottle of Canadian Mist whiskey, probably in a liquor store, circa 1960 (Box 10, Folder 478)
    - Interior portrait of three men in a liquor store with Grand Prize beer, circa 1960 (Box 10, Folder 479)
    - Interior portrait of three women, probably dancers, circa 1960 (Box 10, Folder 480)
    - Interior portrait of two women and three men at the grand opening of a furniture store, circa 1960; 2 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 481)
    - Interior portraits of a man with children and women in a store, circa 1960; 5 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 482)
    - Interior portraits of a woman and man, probably television personalities, with others, circa 1960; 2 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 483)
    - Interior view of a display of bourbons and whiskies, including Bourbon County, Canadian Mist, House of Stuart, Kentucky Gentleman, and Tom Moore, circa 1960 (Box 10, Folder 484)
    - Interior portrait of four women and four men at a banquet, 1961 March 10 (Box 10, Folder 485)
    - Exterior portrait of eleven women standing in front of a woman's club, 1961 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 486)
    - Interior view of a man at a podium and seven men on a stage, 1961 April 15 (Box 10, Folder 487)
    - Interior portrait of a woman, 1961 May 27 (Box 10, Folder 488)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1961 October 7 (Box 10, Folder 489)
    - Interior portrait of four women and a priest, 1961 October 26 (Box 10, Folder 490)
    - Interior portrait of six women on a catwalk stage, 1961 October 26 (Box 10, Folder 491)
    - Interior portrait of a woman being presented an award from two men, 1961 December 18 (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - Interior portrait of three men, 1962 March (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - Interior portrait of a bride and a groom cutting a wedding cake, 1962 August (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Interior portraits from a banquet, including an overview of the hall and discrete images of a woman as well as a woman and man at a microphone, 1962 October; 3 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 495)
    - Interior portrait of a clergyman at a pulpit, 1962 November (Box 10, Folder 496)
    - Interior portrait of two men, 1962 November (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - Exterior portrait of nine women, 1963 March (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Interior portrait of six women and seven men at a bar, 1963 May (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Interior view of photographers at a press conference, 1963 June (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - Studio portrait of a man with a saxophone, 1963 June (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - Interior portrait of a man sitting at microphones, 1963 July (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Interior portrait of six women and eight men, 1963 July (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - Studio portrait of a man, 1963 July (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - Interior portrait of a woman, 1963 August (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - Interior views of a hearing in Los Angeles, California, 1963 August; 2 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Interior views of men and women at a gathering in a residence, 1963 September; 3 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Studio portrait of a man smoking a cigarette, 1963 October (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Exterior view of a woman and a man beside a covered wagon, 1963 November (Box 10, Folder 509)
    - Interior views of a formal event, probably at beauty contest or débutante ball, 1963 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 510)
    - Interior portrait of three women and four men, 1963 December (Box 10, Folder 511)
    - Interior view of attendees leaving a meeting, 1964 February (Box 10, Folder 512)
    - Studio portrait of a woman, 1964 February (Box 10, Folder 513)
    - Exterior view of water line construction along a road, including an Ingersoll & Rand water pump, 1964 March 10 (Box 10, Folder 514)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and two men, 1964 March (Box 10, Folder 515)
    - Interior portrait of two men, 1964 March (Box 10, Folder 516)
    - Interior view of a man at a podium, 1964 March; 2 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 517)
    - Interior view of a man at a podium flanked by a woman and three men at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, 1964 March (Box 10, Folder 518)
    - Interior portraits of a mother and her newborn twins, as well as a portrait of them with a nurse, 1964 May; 3 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 519)
    - Interior views of entertainers, including a female singer and showgirls, probably in Las Vegas, 1964 May; 3 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 520)
    - Interior portrait of a woman posed sitting on a bar, 1964 June (Box 10, Folder 521)
    - Interior views of three women and three girls, probably in a hospital room, 1964 July; 3 photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 522)
    - Exterior portrait of a woman and a clergyman, 1964 August (Box 10, Folder 523)
    - Interior portrait of a bride and a groom as well as another woman, 1964 November (Box 10, Folder 524)
    - Interior portrait of two men, 1964 December (Box 10, Folder 525)
    - Interior portraits from a wedding, which includes the bride and groom as well as a boy, bridesmaid, and two clergymen, 1965 April 11 (Box 11, Folder 526)
    - Interior portrait of two women and a man, 1965 April 22 (Box 11, Folder 527)
    - Exterior portrait of a woman and six men with plans, probably at a construction site, 1965 May 2 (Box 11, Folder 528)
    - Interior view of a crowd at a public hearing, 1965 August 7 (Box 11, Folder 529)
    - Interior portrait of a man, 1965 September 14; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 530)
    - Interior portraits of a man, as well as a group of four other men with him, at a banquet, 1965 October 9; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 531)
    - Exterior portrait of a male photographer, 1965 December 12 (Box 11, Folder 532)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1965 December 18 (Box 11, Folder 533)
    - Exterior portrait of a church choir with 38 members as well as a woman and a clergyman, circa 1965 (Box 11, Folder 534)
    - Exterior portrait of a man in a crowd with television cameras, circa 1965 (Box 11, Folder 535)
    - Exterior portrait of women members of a choir, circa 1965 (Box 11, Folder 536)
    - Interior portrait of four men with each holding a violin, circa 1965 (Box 11, Folder 537)
    - Interior portrait of two women looking at a book for the film, "The Greatest Story Ever Told", circa 1965 (Box 11, Folder 538)
    - Interior portraits of a woman and man at a piano, circa 1965; 3 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 539)
    - Interior portraits of two women, one of them wearing an extravagant hat and mask, and three men, circa 1965; 3 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 540)
    - Interior view of two women, probably counting ballots, surrounded by a group of nine men, circa 1965 (Box 11, Folder 541)
    - View of a crowd waving at people in an automobile, circa 1965 (Box 11, Folder 542)
    - Interior portraits of three men at a bank of microphones, probably at Los Angeles International Airport, circa 1965; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 543)
    - Interior portrait of two men, 1966 January (Box 11, Folder 544)
    - Interior portrait of two men, 1966 February 4 (Box 11, Folder 545)
    - Interior views of proceedings, audience, and press corps at a court hearing, 1966 May 20-25; 3 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 546)
    - Interior view of a woman and four men, probably at a church, 1966 June 7 (Box 11, Folder 547)
    - Interior portrait of two women and a man, 1966 June (Box 11, Folder 548)
    - Interior portrait of two men, 1966 July 26 (Box 11, Folder 549)
    - Studio portrait of a woman, 1966 August 14 (Box 11, Folder 550)
    - Exterior portrait of a girl, woman, and a man, 1966 August 22 (Box 11, Folder 551)
    - Interior portrait of three men, 1966 September 4 (Box 11, Folder 552)
    - Interior portrait of a man, 1966 September 16 (Box 11, Folder 553)
    - Interior portrait of nine men, 1966 September 26 (Box 11, Folder 554)
    - Interior view of a man at a podium at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, 1966 October 28-29 (Box 11, Folder 555)
    - Interior view of a man being interviewed by a male journalist, 1966 November 18 (Box 11, Folder 556)
    - Interior portrait of three men, probably members of a jazz trio, at a piano with drumsticks and a double bass, 1966 December (Box 11, Folder 557)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and two men, 1967 January 8 (Box 11, Folder 558)
    - Interior portrait of a man, 1967 January (Box 11, Folder 559)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1967 January (Box 11, Folder 560)
    - Interior portrait of a man, 1967 February 15 (Box 11, Folder 561)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and three men, 1967 February 15 (Box 11, Folder 562)
    - Interior portrait of a woman at a typewriter, 1967 February (Box 11, Folder 563)
    - Interior portraits of two women and two men, 1967 February; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 564)
    - Interior portraits at a banquet, 1967 April 2; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 565)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, probably at a banquet, 1967 April 18 (Box 11, Folder 566)
    - Interior portrait of two women and a man, 1967 April 24 (Box 11, Folder 567)
    - Interior portrait of three men, 1967 April 27 (Box 11, Folder 568)
    - Exterior portrait of two men and six boys wearing baseball uniforms, 1967 May 20 (Box 11, Folder 569)
    - Exterior view of a funeral procession in a cemetery, including the officiant, pallbearers, and mourners, 1967 May 25 (Box 11, Folder 570)
    - Interior portrait of four men in a liquor store promoting Old Charter Whiskey, 1967 May 26 (Box 11, Folder 571)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1967 May 28 (Box 11, Folder 572)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and two men, 1967 June 18 (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Interior portrait of two women and two men, 1967 June; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - Interior and exterior views related to a funeral, 1967 December 3; 3 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 575)
    - Interior portrait of five men and four women, which includes two of the women holding a check, 1967 December 3 (Box 11, Folder 576)
    - Interior view of a young woman debutante at a ball, circa 1968 (Box 11, Folder 577)
    - Exterior views of children riding and handling horses, including fourteen children, three women, and nine horses, 1969 February 1; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 578)
    - Interior portraits of a man with other men and women, 1969 March 16; 3 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 579)
    - Exterior view of a Buick Electra 225 with a rear fender damaged in an automobile accident, 1969 March 26 (Box 11, Folder 580)
    - Exterior portrait of two women and three men, 1969 April 27 (Box 11, Folder 581)
    - Interior view of a man at a podium with a microphone, 1969 June 29 (Box 11, Folder 582)
    - Interior group portraits from a gathering, 1969 October 17; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 583)
    - Interior portraits of two men as well as discrete portraits of them with a woman and two boys, 1969 October 19; 4 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 584)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1969 November 15 (Box 11, Folder 585)
    - Interior portrait of four men, including a police officer, with a group of eleven children, 1969 December (Box 11, Folder 586)
    - [EMPTY FOLDER] (Box 11, Folder 587)
    - Interior view of a singer and music band performing on a television production stage, 1970 March 8 (Box 11, Folder 588)
    - Interior view of an audience, 1970 June 2 (Box 11, Folder 589)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and two men, 1970 August 25 (Box 11, Folder 590)
    - Exterior portrait of fourteen children, a woman, and a man posed in the ruins of a burned building, circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 591)
    - Interior portraits of a birthday celebration for a woman attended by a man and three women, circa 1970; 2 photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 592)
    - Interior portrait of two women and two men at a banquet, 1971 February (Box 11, Folder 593)
    - Interior portrait of two women and two men, 1972 January 26 (Box 12, Folder 594)
    - Interior portrait of five men, three of the men wearing basketball clothes, at an indoor basketball court, 1972 August (Box 12, Folder 595)
    - Interior portrait of three women and a man, 1972 August (Box 12, Folder 596)
    - Interior portrait of four women, probably at a fashion show on a catwalk, 1972 November (Box 12, Folder 597)
    - Interior portrait of two men playing billiards, 1973 January (Box 12, Folder 598)
    - Interior portraits of groups at a gathering, 1973 January; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 599)
    - Interior portrait of five men, officers of a group with the initials V.K.S., 1973 April (Box 12, Folder 600)
    - Interior portrait of seven women, 1973 April (Box 12, Folder 601)
    - Interior portraits of a boy wearing a Los Angeles Lakers uniform and playing basketball, 1973 May 4; 3 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 602)
    - Interior portrait of five women and two men at a banquet, 1973 May (Box 12, Folder 603)
    - Interior portrait of eleven women and six men, probably at a party in a school, 1973 June (Box 12, Folder 604)
    - Interior portrait of two men and a woman, 1973 June (Box 12, Folder 605)
    - Interior portraits of a male airline pilot with two discrete groups of four women, 1973 June; 3 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 606)
    - Interior portraits of a wedding, including the bride and groom and their attendants, 1973 June; 3 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 607)
    - Exterior portrait of a boy holding a copy of the Los Angeles Sentinel newspaper that commemorates the inauguration of Tom Bradley as mayor of Los Angeles, 1973 July 1 (Box 12, Folder 608)
    - Exterior portraits of a rifle drill team with eight women members that includes a view of their performance with a music band, 1973 July; 3 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 609)
    - Interior portrait of four boys and four men with trophies for baseball, 1973 August (Box 12, Folder 610)
    - Exterior and interior portraits of two women, including a portrait with two men, 1973 September; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 611)
    - Exterior portrait of nine women posed in front of a chartered bus, 1973 October (Box 12, Folder 612)
    - Interior portrait of a large group of men, 1973 November (Box 12, Folder 613)
    - Interior portrait of three women and a man, 1973 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 614)
    - Interior portraits of two women holding trophies for cheerleading, 1973 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 615)
    - Exterior view of three men, including a man dressed as Santa Claus, with a large group of boys and girls, 1973 December (Box 12, Folder 616)
    - Interior portrait of an elderly woman and an elderly man next to a Christmas tree, 1973 December (Box 12, Folder 617)
    - Interior portrait of eight women, each woman holds a rose, 1973 December (Box 12, Folder 618)
    - Exterior portrait of a man posed with a Ford Pinto automobile with advertising for Miller Lite Beer, circa 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 619)
    - Interior portraits related to a presentation, 1974 May 22; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 620)
    - Interior portrait of four women and nine men at the first annual dinner banquet for "CAL-PAC", 1974 May 31 (Box 12, Folder 621)
    - Exterior portrait of a woman with a Cadillac automobile, 1974 June 15 (Box 12, Folder 622)
    - Interior portrait of four women and five men with five of them holding certificates, 1974 June 29 (Box 12, Folder 623)
    - Exterior portrait of four women and three men at a golf course, 1974 August 25 (Box 12, Folder 624)
    - Interior view of two men probably engaged in a mock fight, 1974 November 16 (Box 12, Folder 625)
    - Interior portrait of a woman, 1974 November 23 (Box 12, Folder 626)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1974 November 23 (Box 12, Folder 627)
    - Interior view of people dancing, 1974 November 30 (Box 12, Folder 628)
    - Interior portrait of five women, 1974 November (Box 12, Folder 629)
    - Interior portrait of a girl and man, 1974 December 4 (Box 12, Folder 630)
    - Interior view of children at a winter holidays celebration, 1974 December 7 (Box 12, Folder 631)
    - Interior portraits at an event, 1974 December 23; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 632)
    - Interior portraits, probably from a youth multicultural event, 1975 January 18; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 633)
    - Interior portrait of four women, probably travel agents in a travel agency, 1975 January 23-25; 3 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 634)
    - Exterior portrait of two women and a man, 1975 February 8 (Box 12, Folder 635)
    - Exterior portraits of five women, 1975 March; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 636)
    - Interior portrait of a boy, two women, and a man, 1975 March (Box 12, Folder 637)
    - Interior portrait of five women, 1975 March (Box 12, Folder 638)
    - Interior portrait of nine women, 1975 March; 3 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 639)
    - Interior portrait of three men, 1975 March (Box 12, Folder 640)
    - Interior portrait of two men, 1975 March (Box 12, Folder 641)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1975 April (Box 12, Folder 642)
    - Interior portrait of three women and two men, 1975 May (Box 12, Folder 643)
    - Exterior portrait of a man, 1975 July (Box 12, Folder 644)
    - Interior portrait of five women each wearing a shirt with "fly me" and then their forename, 1975 August (Box 12, Folder 645)
    - Interior portraits of men receiving checks, 1975 August; 7 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 646)
    - Interior portrait of two women, 1975 September (Box 12, Folder 647)
    - Exterior portrait of a boy and a man with a Ford pickup truck with a camper shell, 1975 October (Box 12, Folder 648)
    - Interior portrait of eleven women and seven men, 1975 October (Box 12, Folder 649)
    - Interior portraits of a male captain in the United States Navy, 1975 October; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 650)
    - Interior portraits of a man and woman at desks in a law office, 1975 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 651)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1975 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 652)
    - Interior portrait of eleven women in a nightclub, 1975 November (Box 12, Folder 653)
    - Interior portrait of twelve women, 1975 November (Box 12, Folder 654)
    - Interior portrait of two women and a man, 1975 November (Box 12, Folder 655)
    - Interior portrait of two women and two men, 1975 November (Box 12, Folder 656)
    - Interior view of a banquet with two women and a man in the foreground, 1975 November (Box 12, Folder 657)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man with a wedding cake celebrating their fiftieth wedding anniversary, 1975 December (Box 12, Folder 658)
    - Interior portrait of three women and a man, 1975 December (Box 12, Folder 659)
    - Interior portrait of two men, 1976 January (Box 13, Folder 660)
    - Exterior views of a parade including a boy and woman riding in a convertible automobile and a flag honor guard, 1976 April; 2 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 661)
    - Interior portrait of two men with a bust that depicts one of the men, 1976 May (Box 13, Folder 662)
    - Exterior portrait of a large group of children, women, and men, possibly at a family reunion, 1976 August (Box 13, Folder 663)
    - Interior portrait of four women at an event, 1976 August (Box 13, Folder 664)
    - Interior portrait of two women and a man, 1976 August (Box 13, Folder 665)
    - Interior portrait of a woman, 1976 September (Box 13, Folder 666)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1976 September (Box 13, Folder 667)
    - Interior portrait of travel agents, including eight women and seven men, at an airport, 1976 September (Box 13, Folder 668)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1976 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 669)
    - Interior portraits of a man alone and with a group of a woman and four men, 1976 December; 2 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 670)
    - Interior portrait of three men with a placard advertising Greyhound Lines, 1976–1977 (Box 13, Folder 671)
    - Exterior views of a backyard, which includes two boys playing basketball, 1977 January 8; 3 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 672)
    - Interior portrait of nine women and four men, owners and staff at a restaurant, 1977 February (Box 13, Folder 673)